http://asfabco.com/privacy-policy.html

Our Capabilities Assembly & Equipment
BuildingHeavy Industrial RepairHeavy Metal Fabricating
& Heavy WeldingLarge MachiningSandblasting & Painting
Past Projects
Fabricated Horizontal Vacuum Belt Filter Assembly for the Energy Industry
Fabrication of a Steel Bottom Block Base Assembly for the Primary Aluminum Smelter Industry
Fabricated Steel Sleeve Storage Rack for the Aluminum Industry
Fabrication of a Steel Extruder Base for the Plastics Machinery Builder Industry
Manufacturing of a Dredging Auger Component
Print This PageEmail This Page
Privacy PolicyA & S Fabricating CO. respects your privacy and our site visitors' information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.Information Collected
If you request or submit information to us by sending an Email via info@asfabco.com or by filling out a "contact" form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your Email and other information will not be sold to any third party.Information Collected by Others
This notice addresses only A & S Fabricating CO.'s website policy, and does not apply to sites that users access via links from our site. A & S Fabricating CO. is not responsible for the information collecting policies of other sites, for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, or for the information or content contained therein. Often, links to other websites are provided solely on the basis that they may contain useful information for our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.Cookies
A & S Fabricating CO.'s website does not use cookies. Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information
If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an Email with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information
A & S Fabricating CO. may disclose information when legally compelled to do so: when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so or for the protection of our legal rights.Periodic Policy Changes
Please note that A & S Fabricating CO. reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.This policy statement is made in the name of A & S Fabricating CO. and is effective as of October 1st, 2013. This statement does not create an agreement between A & S Fabricating CO. and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.Contact Us:
A & S Fabricating CO.
265 US Hwy. 431 N.
Copyright © 2019 A & S Fabricating CO.Site created by Thomas Web Solutions
